Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 11: Boxes 636-699
6046
Kheel Center
388.2 linear ft.
Pamphlets, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
The Archives Union File is a collection of publications of United States labor unions. Included is information on the American Institute for Free Labor Development. The AUF collection consists largely of pamphlets and publications of unions, collected by the Kheel Center.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into twelve sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-63
Section 2: Boxes 64-126
Section 3: Boxes 127-191
Section 4: Boxes 192-256
Section 5: Boxes 257-319
Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Section 7: Boxes 379-442
Section 8: Boxes 443-506
Section 9: Boxes 507-571
Section 10: Boxes 572-635
Section 11: Boxes 636-699
Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
AFL-CIO --Archives; AFL-CIO. American Institute for Free Labor Development--Archives; AFL-CIO. Building and Construction Trades Dept.--Archives; AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research--Archives; AFL-CIO. Education Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Executive Council--Archives; AFL-CIO. Human Resources Development Institute--Archives; AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Legislative Department--Archives; AFL-CIO. Public Employees Department--Archives; AFSCME --Archives; Air Line Pilots Association --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Research Department--Archives; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America --Archives; American Association of University Professors --Archives; American Federation of Government Employees --Archives; American Federation of Labor --Archives; American Federation of Musicians --Archives; American Federation of Teachers --Archives; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists --Archives; American Guild of Musical Artists --Archives; American Postal Workers Union --Archives; Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.) --Archives; Bakery, Confectionary and Tobacco Workers International Union --Archives; Coalition of Labor Union Women (U.S.) --Archives; Communication Workers Union --Archives; Communications Workers of America --Archives; Congress of Industrial Organizations --Archives; Federation of Westinghouse Independent Salaried Unions --Archives; Hotel & Restaurant Employees and Bartenders International Union --Archives; Illinois State AFL-CIO --Archives; Industrial Workers of the World --Archives; International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers --Archives; International Association of Fire Fighters --Archives; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers --Archives; International Brotherhood of Painters and Allied Trades --Archives; International Brotherhood of Teamsters --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers Union. Educational Department--Archives; International Longshoremens and Warehousemens Union --Archives; International Typographical Union --Archives; International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; International Union of North American Laborers --Archives; International Union, Allied Industrial Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America --Archives; International Union, United Automobile, Aircraft, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America. Ford Dept. --Archives; International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers --Archives; Jewish Labor Committee (U.S.) --Archives; National Association of Postal Supervisors --Archives; National Maritime Union of America --Archives; National Writers Union (U.S.) --Archives; New York State AFL-CIO --Archives; New York State United Teachers --Archives; Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers International Union --Archives; Screen Actors Guild --Archives; Service Employees International Union --Archives; Sheet Metal Workers International Union --Archives; Teamsters for a Democratic Union --Archives; Textile Workers Union of America --Archives; United Association of Journeymen and Apprentices of the Plumbing and Pipe Fitting Industry --Archives; United Brotherhood of Carpenters and Joiners of America --Archives; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers --Archives; United Glass & Ceramic Workers of North America --Archives; United Mine Workers of America --Archives; United Office and Professionals Workers of America --Archives; United Rubber, Cork, Linoleum and Plastic Workers of America --Archives; United Steelworkers of America --Archives; Utility Workers Union of America --Archives; Writer's Guild of America --Archives
Subjects:
Agricultural laborers--Labor unions; Airlines--Employees--Labor unions; Textile workers--Labor unions; Barbers--Labor unions; Building-service employees--Labor unions; Clothing workers--Labor unions; Construction workers--Labor unions; Automobile industry workers--Labor unions; Bakery employees--Labor unions; Transport workers--Labor unions; Fire fighters--Labor unions; Electricians--Labor unions; Plumbers--Labor unions; Teachers--Labor unions; Glassworkers--Labor unions; Restaurants--Employees--Labor unions; Postal service--Employees--Labor unions; Rubber industry and trade--Labor unions
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this collection:
6046: Archives Union File (AUF)
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 1: Boxes 1-63
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 2: Boxes 64-126
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 3: Boxes 127-191
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 4: Boxes 192-246
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 5: Boxes 257-319
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 7: Boxes 379-442
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 8: Boxes 443-506
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 9: Boxes 507-571
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 10: Boxes 572-635
6046: Archives Union File (AUF), Section 12: Boxes 700-704
Boxes 650-659 and 661-662 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
6046 mf: Archives Union File on Microfilm
CONTAINER LIST
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO; COPE (Box 636, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Program from Appreciation Night, 1995; Publication (Box 636, Folder 1)
    Author: Pennsylvania AFL-CIO; COPE
    Notes: November 5, 1995.
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- AFSCME; Harrisburg Region Central Labor Council, Publication (Box 636, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Program from Annual Awards Dinner, 1990; Publication (Box 636, Folder 2)
    Author: AFSCME; Harrisburg Region Central Labor Council
- United Paperworkers International Union, Publication (Box 636, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Paperworkers, 1979; Publication (Box 636, Folder 3)
    Author: United Paperworkers International Union
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1979:Oct.)
  - Item 2: The Paperworkers, 1979; Publication (Box 636, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.10 (1979:Oct.). Copy 2.
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 636, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Resolutions: Twenty-First Constitutional Convention, 1980; Publication (Box 636, Folder 4)
    Author: Pennsylvania AFL-CIO
    Notes: April 15-18, 1980.
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 636, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania AFL-CIO News, 1979; Publication (Box 636, Folder 5)
    Author: Pennsylvania AFL- CIO
    Notes: v.20:no.4 (1997:Oct.)
- Citizens Voice, Publication (Box 636, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Citizens Voice, 1984; Publication (Box 636, Folder 6)
    Author: Citizens Voice
    Notes: September 29, 1984.
  - Item 2: Citizens Voice, 1987; Publication (Box 636, Folder 6)
    Notes: October 9, 1987.
  - Item 3: Citizens Voice, 1990; Publication (Box 636, Folder 6)
    Notes: June 14, 1990.
  - Item 4: Citizens Voice, 1990; Publication (Box 636, Folder 6)
    Notes: September 1, 1990.
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO; COPE, Publication (Box 636, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Program - Seventh Annual Dinner, 1987; Publication (Box 636, Folder 7)
    Author: Greater Wilkes- Barre Labor Council
    Notes: September 10, 1987.
  - Item 2: Program for A Night at the Races, 1990; Publication (Box 636, Folder 7)
    Notes: May 2, 1990.
  - Item 3: Samuel Julius Bianco Testimonial Dinner, 1992; Publication (Box 636, Folder 7)
    Author: Greater Wilkes-Barre Labor Council; ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers Union)
    Notes: October 16, 1992. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Pennsylvania AFL-CIO News: COPE Newsletter, 1997; Publication (Box 636, Folder 7)
    Notes: January, 1997.
- UMW (United Mine Workers of America), Publication (Box 636, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: College education financing: IUE members' guide, 1969; Publication (Box 636, Folder 8)
    Author: IUE (International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers)
  - Item 2: United Mine Workers Journal: Proud to be a Miner, 1976; Publication (Box 636, Folder 8)
    Author: UMW (United Mine Workers of America)
    Notes: v.87:no.11 (1976:June 15/July 15). A Special Bicentennial Issue
- Southern Combed Yarn Spinners Association, Publication (Box 636, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Faces we see, 1939; Publication (Box 636, Folder 9)
    Author: Mildred Gwin Barnwell; Bill Baker
- CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women), Publication (Box 636, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: First biennial convention, Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1979; Publication (Box 636, Folder 10)
    Author: CLUW (Coalition of Labor Union Women)
    Notes: September 13-16, 1979, Hotel Statler, New York City
- ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union), Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Justice vs J.P. Stevens: Testimony, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Author: ACTWU (Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union)
    Notes: Advertisement. Copy 2.
  - Item 2: The Struggle for economic justice at J.P. Stevens, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: What's Under the Covers, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Who is J. P. Stevens?, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
  - Item 5: Fact Sheet: J. P. Stevens and Its Record of Discrimination in Employment Practices, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Notes: JPS-1A
  - Item 6: Fact Sheet: J. P. Stevens: The Company, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Notes: JPS-2A
  - Item 7: Fact Sheet: J. P. Stevens and Occupational Safety and Health, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Notes: JPS-4A
  - Item 8: Fact Sheet: J. P. Stevens and the Improverishment of the Carolinas, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Notes: JPS-5
  - Item 9: Fact Sheet: J. P. Stevens and the Law, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Notes: JPS-6A
  - Item 10: Fact Sheet: J. P. Stevens Has Pursued a Runaway Shop Policy, Stranding Thousands of Northern Workers in Closed Plants, Publication (Box 636, Folder 11)
    Notes: JPS-8A
- Northeastern Pennsylvania Building and Construction Trades Council, Publication (Box 636, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Testimonial Dinner honoring Albert Sutcavage, 1979; Publication (Box 636, Folder 12)
    Author: Northeastern Pennsylvania Building and Construction Trades Council
    Notes: Program
- SEIU (Service Employees International Union), Publication (Box 636, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: News and Views, 1981; Publication (Box 636, Folder 13)
    Author: International Printing and Graphic Communications Union
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1981:Jan.)
  - Item 2: Service Employee, 1980; Publication (Box 636, Folder 13)
    Author: SEIU (Service Employees International Union)
    Notes: v.40:no.2 (1980:Sep.)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO; COPE Committee, Publication (Box 637, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Program from A Night at the Races, 1992; Publication (Box 637, Folder 1)
    Author: Pennsylvania AFL-CIO; COPE Committee
    Notes: March 25, 1992.
- Northeast AFL-CIO Alliance of Retiree Organizations, Publication (Box 637, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Program from A Tribute to our Mae McHugh, 1993; Publication (Box 637, Folder 2)
    Author: Northeast AFL-CIO Alliance of Retiree Organizations
    Notes: July 30, 1993.
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America. Local 1, Publication (Box 637, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Lithopinion, 1972; Publication (Box 637, Folder 3)
    Author: Amalgamated Lithographers of America. Local 1
    Notes: v.7:no.2:issue 26 (1972:Summer)
  - Item 2: Lithopinion, 1972; Publication (Box 637, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.7:no.2:issue 26 (1972:Summer). Copy 2.
- Amalgamated Lithographers of America. Local 1, Publication (Box 637, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Lithopinion, 1973; Publication (Box 637, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.8:no.1:issue 29 (1973:Spring)
  - Item 2: Lithopinion, 1974; Publication (Box 637, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.9:no.3:issue 35 (1974:Fall)
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 637, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Officers' report: The Challenge for the Future, 1985; Publication (Box 637, Folder 5)
    Notes: 26th annual convention, June 11-14, 1985.
- UNITE! Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department, Publication (Box 637, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: UNITE! Insight, 1997; Publication (Box 637, Folder 6)
    Author: UNITE! Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1997:Nov.)
  - Item 2: UNITE! Insight, 1997; Publication (Box 637, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.4:no.1 (1997:Nov.). Copy 2.
  - Item 3: The Union News, 1999; Publication (Box 637, Folder 6)
    Author: The Union News
    Notes: Labor's Voice of Northeastern Pennsylvania. May 1999.
  - Item 4: Labor Management Newsletter, 1994; Publication (Box 637, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1994:June/July)
- ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union), Publication (Box 637, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Union Worker, 1972; Publication (Box 637, Folder 7)
    Author: ILGWU (International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union)
    Notes: September, 1972. Pages 3 and 4 only.
  - Item 2: Northeast News, 1972; Publication (Box 637, Folder 7)
    Notes: September, 1972.
- Pennsylvania AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 637, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania AFL-CIO News COPE newsletter, 1985; Publication (Box 637, Folder 8)
    Notes: June, 1985.
  - Item 2: Leadership Linews, 1999; Publication (Box 637, Folder 8)
    Author: Leadership Wilkes- Barre
    Notes: v.7:no.3 (1999:Summer)
  - Item 3: Proposed Consitutional Changes, recommended by the Executive Council, 1984; Publication (Box 637, Folder 8)
- UNITE! Northeast, Western Pennsylvania and Ohio Department, Publication (Box 637, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: UNITE! Insight, 1996; Publication (Box 637, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.2:no.1 (1996:Feb.)
  - Item 2: Citizens Voice, 1991; Publication (Box 637, Folder 9)
    Notes: August 31, 1991.
- Union Label and Service Trades Council, Publication (Box 637, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: 58th Annual Convention, 1996; Publication (Box 637, Folder 10)
    Author: Union Label and Service Trades Council
    Notes: September 14-15, 1996
- UNITE!, Publication (Box 637, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: UNITE!, 1996; Publication (Box 637, Folder 11)
    Author: UNITE!
    Notes: v.2:no.5 (1996:Sep./Oct.)
- The Union News, Publication (Box 637, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: The Union News, 1993; Publication (Box 637, Folder 12)
    Notes: Labor's Voice of Northeastern Pennsylvania. April 1993
  - Item 2: The Union News, 1993; Publication (Box 637, Folder 12)
    Notes: Labor's Voice of Northeastern Pennsylvania. May 1993
  - Item 3: The Union News, 1993; Publication (Box 637, Folder 12)
    Notes: Labor's Voice of Northeastern Pennsylvania. June 1993
  - Item 4: The Union News, 1997; Publication (Box 637, Folder 12)
    Notes: Labor's Voice of Northeastern Pennsylvania. July 1997
  - Item 5: The Union News, 1997; Publication (Box 637, Folder 12)
    Notes: Labor's Voice of Northeastern Pennsylvania. July 1997. Copy 2.
- AFSCME. District Council 87, Publication (Box 637, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Frank Schubert, 1995; Publication (Box 637, Folder 13)
    Author: AFSCME. District Council 87
    Notes: Testimonial dinner program. May 11, 1995.
  - Item 2: Men of the Year, 1996, Senator Ray Musto, Senator Bob Mellow. Congratulations Senators from all of us, Publication (Box 637, Folder 13)
    Author: Northeastern PA District 3 Council of Retirees
    Notes: Testimonial dinner program. May 31, 1996.
  - Item 3: Program from the 75th Anniversary Dinner-Dance, 1997; Publication (Box 637, Folder 13)
    Author: International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 401
- Pennsylvania Fire Fighters' Association, Publication (Box 637, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania Professional Fire Fighter, 1983; Publication (Box 637, Folder 14)
    Author: Pennsylvania Fire Fighters' Association
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1983:Apr.)
  - Item 2: Pennsylvania Professional Fire Fighter, 1983; Publication (Box 637, Folder 14)
    Notes: v.8:no.1 (1983:Apr.). Copy 2.
- Pennsylvania State University. Dept. of Labor Studies, Publication (Box 637, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania labor, 1982; Publication (Box 637, Folder 15)
    Author: Pennsylvania State University. Dept. of Labor Studies
    Notes: Fall 1982
  - Item 2: Pennsylvania labor, Publication (Box 637, Folder 15)
    Notes: Special Issue
- Pennsylvania Labor History Society, Publication (Box 637, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Pennsylvania Labor History Notes, 1982; Publication (Box 637, Folder 16)
    Author: Pennsylvania Labor History Society
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1982:Oct.)
- Roosevelt University. Labor Education Division, Publication (Box 638, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor leadership in a dynamic society; a 32-week certificate program for the academic year 1966-1967, 1965-1966 (Box 638, Folder 1)
    Author: Harry Kurshenbaum
- Hart, Schaffner & Marx, Publication (Box 638, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Behind the seams, 1961; Publication (Box 638, Folder 2)
    Author: Hart, Schaffner & Marx
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 638, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Official Souvenir of the Fourth Biennial Convention, 1920; Publication (Box 638, Folder 3)
    Author: ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America)
    Notes: May 10-15, 1920. Brittle
- ACWA (Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America), Publication (Box 638, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Souvenir of the Sixth Biennial Convention, 1924; Publication (Box 638, Folder 4)
    Notes: May 12-17, 1924. Brittle
- AFL-CIO. Dept. of Economic Research, Publication (Box 639, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Recession 1991: ease the pain, create jobs, Publication (Box 639, Folder 1)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Dept. of Economic Research
    Notes: February 1991.
- AFL-CIO. Dept. of Economic Research, Publication (Box 639, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: We need more jobs: more good jobs, 1994; Publication (Box 639, Folder 2)
    Notes: February 1994.
- New York (State). Dept. of Labor. Division of Research and Statistics, Publication (Box 639, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Labor area summary. Monthly statistical report, 1997; Publication (Box 639, Folder 3)
    Author: New York (State). Dept. of Labor. Division of Research and Statistics
    Notes: v.9:no.12 (1997:Dec.). October 1997 Data
  - Item 2: Labor area summary. Monthly statistical report, 1998; Publication (Box 639, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.7 (1998:July). May 1998 Data.
  - Item 3: Labor area summary. Monthly statistical report, 1998; Publication (Box 639, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.7 (1998:July). May 1998 Data. Copy 2.
  - Item 4: Labor area summary. Monthly statistical report, 1998; Publication (Box 639, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.8 (1990:Aug.). June 1998 Data.
  - Item 5: Labor area summary. Monthly statistical report, 1998; Publication (Box 639, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.10:no.9 (1998:Sep.). July 1998 Data.
- AFSCME, Publication (Box 639, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Jobs for the future: an AFL-CIO view, 1987; Publication (Box 639, Folder 4)
    Author: Thomas R. Donahue
    Notes: Publication no.179
  - Item 2: Government for sale: An Examination of the Contracting Out of State and Local Government Services, Publication (Box 639, Folder 4)
    Author: AFSCME
    Notes: 4th edtion
  - Item 3: The Privatization / contracting out debate, 1988; Publication (Box 639, Folder 4)
- Institute for Labor Education and Research, Publication (Box 639, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Corporate game plan, 1981; Publication (Box 639, Folder 5)
    Author: Institute for Labor Education and Research
- AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Dept., Publication (Box 639, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Trade crisis: time for action, 1984; Publication (Box 639, Folder 6)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Industrial Union Dept.
- Citizen Action, Publication (Box 639, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Economic expose: Who's Stealing Your Job and Picking Your Pocket and What You Can Do About It, 1983; Publication (Box 639, Folder 7)
    Author: Steve Max
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Ammo, 1991; Publication (Box 639, Folder 8)
    Author: UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America)
    Notes: v.27:no.6 (1991:Apr.)
  - Item 2: I pledge allegiance to the corporate state of America, 1978; Publication (Box 639, Folder 8)
    Author: William W. Winpisinger
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Stop the trade gap, 1987; Publication (Box 639, Folder 9)
- Institute for Labor Education and Research, Publication (Box 639, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: The Economy: who's holding up who?, Publication (Box 639, Folder 10)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Changing information services: Strategies for Workers and Consumers, 1994; Publication (Box 639, Folder 11)
    Author: CWA (Communications Workers of America)
- AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research, Publication (Box 639, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: America needs a raise, 1996; Publication (Box 639, Folder 12)
    Author: AFL-CIO. Department of Economic Research
    Notes: Publication no.O-T95-0296-1
- Union Communication Services, Publication (Box 639, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: How often has this happened to you?, Publication (Box 639, Folder 13)
    Author: Union Communication Services
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Principles of arbitration and cross-examination, 1976; Publication (Box 639, Folder 14)
- CWA (Communications Workers of America), Publication (Box 639, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Mobilizing for the '90s, 1991; Publication (Box 639, Folder 15)
- CSEA (Civil Service Employees Association), Publication (Box 639, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: CSEA News and Letters: how to get one going or make one better, 1981; Publication (Box 639, Folder 16)
    Author: CSEA (Civil Service Employees Association)
- UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America). Public Relations & Publications Dept., Publication (Box 639, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Spotlight on your union: how to write news releases that get the media's attention, 1987; Publication (Box 639, Folder 17)
    Author: UAW (International Union, United Automobile, Aerospace, and Agricultural Implement Workers of America). Public Relations & Publications Dept.